Denes Csala: Right?
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: relationship, which is bad to get blah blah, blah, follow Canadian submit capability.
Denes Csala: can we delete the Pdf, so 8 k, $2. Follow me
Denes Csala: right
Denes Csala: that you can't belt onto. So
Denes Csala: again, a dashboard file with public control online dashboard link that's gonna be able to pay the effort.
Denes Csala: Ta-ta!
Denes Csala: It makes sense that
Denes Csala: it's convert.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: I should hear what you get in
Denes Csala: move their settings with hoops on one of the question.
Denes Csala: Hold on the call, what's the email.
Denes Csala: what are not here?
Denes Csala: Thank you.
Denes Csala: yeah.
Denes Csala: but it goes to talk
Denes Csala: just to complete
Denes Csala: it's great entitled finance, active it up it. It can't tell me. Now, hold.
Denes Csala: okay, it's like a big gig.
Denes Csala: Unush.
Denes Csala: Nope.
Denes Csala: how's making you check it?
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: come in.
Denes Csala: Thank you.
Denes Csala: Yes.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: Yeah. There's no payment. Copy articles yet
Denes Csala: are coming to niche, admitted you get back in case you start.
Denes Csala: How's it going to do but educate as as an agent don't.
Denes Csala: That's what needs that key and
Denes Csala: Puerto Rica together. Which which one?
Denes Csala: It's a great
Denes Csala: and
Denes Csala: yeah, it took power down to work.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: But yeah, I could still be able to look which one
Denes Csala: digital analytics track agent.
Denes Csala: And each of these capabilities that there.
Denes Csala: yeah, let me make one. Now.
Denes Csala: No, that's okay.
Denes Csala: Hello.
Denes Csala: And as a customer student.
Denes Csala: that's all. Publican at the end
Denes Csala: system may forget disclaimers my best to do it and Sb.
Denes Csala: Access.
Denes Csala: I can check our Chicago one. Now
Denes Csala: let's keep. Let's keep the Ikea sheet, and he's got to
Denes Csala: to, the, and one of which was so he said,
Denes Csala: but it's not for a day.
Denes Csala: So bottom part of your account.
Denes Csala: Hmm.
Denes Csala: The 30 king.
Denes Csala: Now you know. What's the guy left at us? Phone button?
Denes Csala: Awesome.
Denes Csala: Thank you.
Denes Csala: Glanced as it mentioned by this code bar.
Denes Csala: Edo is electric.
Denes Csala: Let's see, let's look at this.
Denes Csala: Let's see if that indicate.
Denes Csala: So
Denes Csala: actually not looking at Beta because it's not put forward yet.
Denes Csala: You thanks.
Denes Csala: Okay, this is an Sd.
Denes Csala: You.
Denes Csala: We don't forget to the cannabis access here into the shop.
Denes Csala: Cool.
Denes Csala: No issue across from time.
Denes Csala: Not that heavy like coming home. I think it.
Denes Csala: It took the younger 5, of course, can advocate here.
Denes Csala: So let me see.
Denes Csala: Yeah, please talk. So please, talk would be in.
Denes Csala: Yeah, because
Denes Csala: and each and
Denes Csala: okay.
Denes Csala: dashboard
Denes Csala: shazanik phone call.
Denes Csala: Pretty sure some requests for you.
Denes Csala: But can I have this, you will actually not
Denes Csala: pretty much. Oh, fishing!
Denes Csala: Oh, love it!
Denes Csala: Let me ask me with yet another machine language.
Denes Csala: am I correct? Order or not?
Denes Csala: And then, if you thought occur
Denes Csala: most, we could make your hotels neighborhood Keith leaders to keep us.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: as we thought, of course, the terminal setup
Denes Csala: sure standard I might provide to get through the not your correct windows phone.
Denes Csala: And of course.
Denes Csala: do you want
Denes Csala: compost?
Denes Csala: Sure could have a better set of
Denes Csala: people.
Denes Csala: Yeah, thanks for the power sharing.
Denes Csala: Don't look at compose extension. Update
Denes Csala: your track, docker extension. There you go.
Denes Csala: Esta could is I have you like
Denes Csala: Prime Minister says I pay frequently. What is the Major?
Denes Csala: Sure? Couldn't
Denes Csala: I try a port on foot shocker
Denes Csala: as antadic?
Denes Csala: Oh, not declared as external, but could not be found network that
Denes Csala: my kid is because he just
Denes Csala: okay, does. It costs on this, too.
Denes Csala: Network can't be, can't be as a good as a good linear product
Denes Csala: at Docker, the dock docker network, create web name, docker, create network web.
Denes Csala: Yes.
Denes Csala: thank you.
Denes Csala: Let's see a joke
Denes Csala: mean that we're
Denes Csala: oh, okay, think we are.
Denes Csala: The local host had
Denes Csala: oaks, California.
Denes Csala: British waters
Denes Csala: with your local host of CPU and get 9 meters. Right?
Denes Csala: Computer doesn't matter. According to case. You know, Jupiter
Denes Csala: posture.
Denes Csala: Let's find your spot
Denes Csala: as as a associated with me.
Denes Csala: I'll make an image.
Denes Csala: What's name internal? It was external.
Denes Csala: Yeah
Denes Csala: record as in which, if Mariroga took a park order the Etocher mechanisms.
Denes Csala: That's right.
Denes Csala: Security flow.
Denes Csala: But.
Denes Csala: of course. And now see if dashboard monitor we want.
Denes Csala: It's funny.
Denes Csala: A new dashboard
Denes Csala: tools with us.
Denes Csala: Turn it on default settings.
Denes Csala: There you go.
Denes Csala: Start opening. The kit made me dashboard
Denes Csala: shoot
Denes Csala: favorite
Denes Csala: most.
Denes Csala: So cozype team to Sahara was a 4th like username. It'll
Denes Csala: so it will default very funny
Denes Csala: home dashboard or sled again as a new dashboard.
Denes Csala: So experiment Sds.
Denes Csala: A credit becomes a safe, safe dashboard
Denes Csala: as in each water symbol. Dot choke you, partner. Level is good.
Denes Csala: You could hit the provisioning
Denes Csala: port as a default port, of course.
Denes Csala: Get you close
Denes Csala: same time. Optional mega approval on your rms registered to local
Denes Csala: as it means, let's zoom real quick.
Denes Csala: Yes, also it
Denes Csala: the compost OP with less Tokyo compost damage.
Denes Csala: does she?
Denes Csala: You know I thought not sure about that cool.
Denes Csala: absolute version is obsolete.
Denes Csala: It will be ignored. Please don't retouch. It's gonna be your version.
Denes Csala: excuse me
Denes Csala: after it was not a ninja, certainly
Denes Csala: an Internet Internet container for log
Denes Csala: chocolate.
Denes Csala: No bye.
Denes Csala: which is also in which for.
Denes Csala: But as I would like we're doing.
Denes Csala: That's a no
Denes Csala: authentication token.
Denes Csala: Look at, accept.
Denes Csala: Would you be there?
Denes Csala: Awesome?
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: What the heck is that
Denes Csala: correct? As we partner slide or
Denes Csala: we go.
Denes Csala: You'll be there a second because of the browser instead, sir.
Denes Csala: And yeah, said, you get Kt as a guitar, as a catalog balance report.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: if installed on those, it's all I do actually alright install influx ebit.
Denes Csala: it says you can let the up
Denes Csala: influx TV.
Denes Csala: But
Denes Csala: anyway.
Denes Csala: Hello, the letters? Okay, all of users and all of password, though.
Denes Csala: occur which internal network, as as as a human.
Denes Csala: as a starter.
Denes Csala: Yeah, as it generated. Okay?
Denes Csala: And you know, sweet.
Denes Csala: yeah, sure.
Denes Csala: Awesome. No, no, not as bad as a freak.
Denes Csala: Of course it's called a hostages of the position
Denes Csala: we're starting to grow for now do? Carlos had a musician, but it wasn't later edge order, for
Denes Csala: also I took that because all of baked in as influx TV
Denes Csala: make it one not yet low key. Make elasticsearch Mysql. Postgres in a field inclusive. It's electric
Denes Csala: Elliot Ethulet
Denes Csala: default the database as a never base save and test. Yes, but the source is working now. Of course
Denes Csala: it
Denes Csala: of the influx of the edge.
Denes Csala: This request, Tricky, you know, around later who's
Denes Csala: later as a user Esaki said, Packet, educate pandas.
Denes Csala: Daughter frame.
Denes Csala: It was 2 PM.
Denes Csala: Index on the value in a custom category.
Denes Csala: a measurement
Denes Csala: evolution field column look also calls sample right? Sample here as a value.
Denes Csala: Oh, so make music.
Denes Csala: It's the solo video which will stand and kick.
Denes Csala: What's this Sunday language?
Denes Csala: H,
Denes Csala: as
Denes Csala: visualization filter grouped by.
Denes Csala: yeah, that's true. What's wrong, though let's pull that page. No.
Denes Csala: which I said that you're on the wall.
Denes Csala: A good effort.
Denes Csala: It automatically include edit.
Denes Csala: And I can get the base in a measurement.
Denes Csala: And Kirk last 5 min
Denes Csala: connect dual values when you connect your story always. Otherwise, let's say, problem.
Denes Csala: Right management
Denes Csala: case is for save same streaming on autosh
Denes Csala: dashboard of a preserved. I don't know
Denes Csala: as much as you just get me as a question.
Denes Csala: I wish, my God, it will.
Denes Csala: Inventive wheel!
Denes Csala: I don't have to be interested.
Denes Csala: Then I'm familiar with that's it
Denes Csala: streaming out of the
Denes Csala: look.
Denes Csala: What happened.
Denes Csala: Let's not get good to zoom commercial today.
Denes Csala: I can't spot the story made sense
Denes Csala: about the calendar
Denes Csala: less.
Denes Csala: My goodness, you got good.
Denes Csala: thank you.
Denes Csala: Awesome.
Denes Csala: It was like, you know.
Denes Csala: basically the keys.
Denes Csala: But volume of 39 persistent volume
Denes Csala: with my cosm or
Denes Csala: so.
Denes Csala: Well, it
Denes Csala: okay.
Denes Csala: which is.
Denes Csala: But you know.
Denes Csala: oh.
Denes Csala: one of them.
Denes Csala: So maybe
Denes Csala: I don't say one.
Denes Csala: Thank you.
Denes Csala: Just intentionally available. Right?
Denes Csala: That's trying to get a number.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: possibility.
Denes Csala: Okay, so let's see attention on me.
Denes Csala: The meetings
Denes Csala: kind of in the data.
Denes Csala: What that
Denes Csala: gonna be?
Denes Csala: Editor?
Denes Csala: Give me the rules.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: that's cool.
Denes Csala: It's
Denes Csala: right. That's Platform.
Denes Csala: who's listening can also look for that notification.
Denes Csala: Perfect
Denes Csala: holds up.
Denes Csala: No, that's okay.
Denes Csala: So could you explain? You know, it gives you 7.
Denes Csala: Let me not show that.
Denes Csala: Yeah, that looks good.
Denes Csala: Okay?
Denes Csala: So so
Denes Csala: you know that.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: awesome. Can we do that?
Denes Csala: Junk?
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: no. People didn't come in here. Okay, well.
Denes Csala: legal administer optimization items.
Denes Csala: Okay?
Denes Csala: Oh, wait.
Denes Csala: that's see.
Denes Csala: But that's true. But
Denes Csala: if it's so.
Denes Csala: it's fine.
Denes Csala: We don't like any work
Denes Csala: a bit. Snack approval.
Denes Csala: The
Denes Csala: please go on.
Denes Csala: Good.
Denes Csala: No, thank you.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: 5.
Denes Csala: Very good product.
Denes Csala: Oh.
Denes Csala: I don't think we need to do.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: Oh.
Denes Csala: thank you.
Denes Csala: Web account.
Denes Csala: Yes.
Denes Csala: restart always.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: but
Denes Csala: perfect.
Denes Csala: But
Denes Csala: meet
Denes Csala: Jackie Restart always tell you the deal.
Denes Csala: Yes.
Denes Csala: for New York.
Denes Csala: is it? And that's what it is.
Denes Csala: And
Denes Csala: the past.
Denes Csala: Yeah, seriously, wasn't it.
Denes Csala: That's what he's happening.
Denes Csala: That's actually let me see.
Denes Csala: Perfect.
Denes Csala: beautiful.
Denes Csala: that's all possible.
Denes Csala: It's the development.
Denes Csala: And we all send them.
Denes Csala: that's see good
Denes Csala: interface, default config location.
Denes Csala: and it looks fast as well. Yes.
Denes Csala: at at a good default.
Denes Csala: Okay, let's just check like a closed door.
Denes Csala: and those I think I would go with per meta based.com as of
Denes Csala: running metabase on docker is big tests
Denes Csala: to persist data outside of the container and make it available for use between container launches.
Denes Csala: We can mount a local file path inside our container.
Denes Csala: Okay? Okay, environment.
Denes Csala: Those environment, then be some mechanic and
Denes Csala: volume metabase dot or metabase. We know it works. We know it works metabase, dot world.
Denes Csala: Here we go.
Denes Csala: And
Denes Csala: okay.
Denes Csala: that's good, sound, good.
Denes Csala: That's good.
Denes Csala: This is
Denes Csala: okay.
Denes Csala: She needs to go.
Denes Csala: This will be part of your taxes.
Denes Csala: This is pop up.
Denes Csala: Phone told us that Nope
Denes Csala: understood.
Denes Csala: That is a little.
Denes Csala: Yep.
Denes Csala: if I remember.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: bear with me.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: in terms of still hasn't
Denes Csala: partner type.
Denes Csala: Let me check.
Denes Csala: Yeah, that's awesome.
Denes Csala: Feels good.
Denes Csala: First, st
Denes Csala: it's okay.
Denes Csala: Post. This should have you.
Denes Csala: They should work.
Denes Csala: What's that?
Denes Csala: Okay?
Denes Csala: Also the same purpose.
Denes Csala: What's think?
Denes Csala: It's good?
Denes Csala: Answer. The next thing.
Denes Csala: Thank you for the response.
Denes Csala: you know. And also, yeah.
Denes Csala: well, let's see.
Denes Csala: okay.
Denes Csala: shut up metabase dock. One interesting
Denes Csala: as an environment variable less
Denes Csala: this code username
Denes Csala: and not it as as a complete z as a cause environment variable, of course.
Denes Csala: Good.
Denes Csala: Oh, cool. It doesn't work for me that most of which have
Denes Csala: that megaitical container. Kit.
Denes Csala: We don't okay outlook within the duplicate.
Denes Csala: Of course, Kate Restock, Kate Restock, is it?
Denes Csala: Nature? Jupiter, international geographer knows. Make it to land.
Denes Csala: Stand by it.
Denes Csala: Why do you? And you don't done it yet.
Denes Csala: I don't mention
Denes Csala: that's oh, that's regular. That's standard.
Denes Csala: Nice workshop.
Denes Csala: you, Peter said. That you be there.
Denes Csala: Oh, that thing bizarre!
Denes Csala: See? It looked like
Denes Csala: what you remind me is like a presenter. She would
Denes Csala: the 8
Denes Csala: magnesodel, Yoga, short and 59,
Denes Csala: also s. 3 50 s. 3 p. Hq. Group
Denes Csala: image.
Denes Csala: Know that we're trying in your little thought right?
Denes Csala: Oh, can you look at it
Denes Csala: still talking? Telephone the volume as a permanent star here for later?
Denes Csala: Hey? Okay, preventative path
Denes Csala: won't distinguish because I didn't care. Again.
Denes Csala: Good occurrence, as I can say.
Denes Csala: a good academic I don't know.
Denes Csala: hey? Whatever as as invented it
Denes Csala: as it will object.
Denes Csala: A bunny chimp.
Denes Csala: Stupid! Everyone says I should cross the started back.
Denes Csala: That default was set up by empty.
Denes Csala: No.
Denes Csala: you
Denes Csala: be equal to them with the vote.
Denes Csala: Me, too.
Denes Csala: Well, we 1st of all the other branches is
Denes Csala: to get a dish maybe a decade ago
Denes Csala: wanted to follow up with those out.
Denes Csala: We're the only get a meta based for snar.
Denes Csala: A very good marsh again.
Denes Csala: as you should. Yeah, yeah. No shirt
Denes Csala: lip.
Denes Csala: awkward music. Make hood.
Denes Csala: Then we go south with your
Denes Csala: and we're gonna support. We're gonna add a Google map, pop all over the chat.
Denes Csala: of course.
Denes Csala: Took my camera.
Denes Csala: Did you actually did. You have to go through?
Denes Csala: Hold on!
Denes Csala: Hold
Denes Csala: has no search as a as a chat blast at this point.
Denes Csala: Awesome.
Denes Csala: Yeah.
Denes Csala: Export your message as well.
Denes Csala: One of me. Or tonight.
Denes Csala: yeah, I 5 Mv.
Denes Csala: just.
Denes Csala: And we're back here that we don't watch me
Denes Csala: for the classic kernel.
Denes Csala: Fantastic.
Denes Csala: Okay, yeah. I think, as Alexa man, obviously, and accept that too.
Denes Csala: It's in there.
Denes Csala: Hello!
Denes Csala: Most customers who I think we don't.
Denes Csala: Yes, also, my good one.
Denes Csala: start yours right here, we can support you.
Denes Csala: Actually, what's the S. 3?
Denes Csala: Keep us at the same.
Denes Csala: Let's look at the quote level
Denes Csala: music.
Denes Csala: It's a couple of good shit.
Denes Csala: E, okay, yeah, that's your interest.
Denes Csala: No.
Denes Csala: yeah.
Denes Csala: I made a hard time. I was talking about this issue.
Denes Csala: Okay, excellent.
Denes Csala: With your
Denes Csala: period, being able to make me as a desic at all, as a cataly to be.
Denes Csala: but to the to the itinerary
Denes Csala: as 6 matrix one.
Denes Csala: Because.
Denes Csala: could, you know, like Penny gets on the nationality without, even
Denes Csala: as if you don't mean that, much less I
Denes Csala: board
Denes Csala: at convert. I look type format cottegorio.
Denes Csala: I mean, if you compare the resource, for it pulls our finance value in the.
Denes Csala: of course.
Denes Csala: May chopotog
Denes Csala: mean the ticket together.
Denes Csala: He had to. If I make this one too.
Denes Csala: build up reactant cross, trace the same exactly like that which one is
Denes Csala: mention in the 1st table.
Denes Csala: Correct? Yeah. The music.
Denes Csala: Let's see if
Denes Csala: team chat. Remember as email history was as I get private.
Denes Csala: perfect.
Denes Csala: Okay for Missouri and Belgia
Denes Csala: from India.
Denes Csala: But one of the big pockets. It's just since you're Marchella Nope food ticket.
Denes Csala: That's my
Denes Csala: be helpful.
Denes Csala: It won't be able to.
Denes Csala: You can create an email
Denes Csala: as as a problem at the differential one.
Denes Csala: A good bacteria research objective. Also
Denes Csala: go ahead. This is next.
Denes Csala: but not not my kids.
Denes Csala: can you? It's not good.
Denes Csala: And that's exactly.
Denes Csala: Or the test was checking again.
Denes Csala: Okay.
Denes Csala: and if there's a typical phone group, right or awkward or
Denes Csala: or scenarios.
Denes Csala: but not really.